We have a lot of them lined up in the store next to ours.
There were a lot of them.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, then.
Manjuu and
Yes, ma'am.
Dumplings?
Yes.
I've been here before.
Yes, I have.
What do you like? You like it?
Yeah, it's fun.
I don't know, like a car ride.
Oh! Like a car.
I was gonna do that.
I like it.
It's fun.
Wow, thank you. I'm glad you like it. Can you hear me?
Okay, what would you like to say to your fans?
You're cute. Thank you. See you later.
I'm going to get some souvenirs.
Bye bye.
Bye. Thank you.
It's started! TENTABY!
Hello. As of September 28th.
I'm Ten, now 18 years old and an adult!
Hello, I'd like to do a project called "Ten Tabi" for the first time on youtube.
I'd like to do a project called "Ten Tabi" on youtube for the first time!
Today's destination is...
Amazing hot spring fields!Kusatsu! Amazing hot-spring fields!
Amazing! The members of that group!
Rika Ishimori introduced her hometown to us at Sakurazaka when she had the time!
It was a bit of a battle for the location, but she didn't get it, but I've been pushing for Gunma for a long time, so...
I'm here... all by myself!
Let's go on a trip!
Amazing!
So cute!
It's hot, hot, hot.
Look at this.
Oh, my gosh.
Ta-da!
Amazing!
Like this.
Ta-da!
This is Yubatake!
Wow!
Amazing!
Look at this!
It's like emerald green!
Why is it so green?
It's so beautiful!
Wow!
Can you touch the steam?
Smells so good!
It feels so good! I haven't taken a walk this slow in a long time.
Nice! Entering a narrow street
Very nice atmosphereVery nice atmosphere
Chopstick shop?
Chopstick shop!
Beautiful!
Look!
It's so cute!
So cute!
Look!
I want some chicken wings.
I like the eringi.
I always buy the plain ones.
But I definitely want wings!
I'll get the wings!
Okay, I'll get wings and...
I want to decorate it with something, so it's more like a bridge.
Oh, it's so cute! But you know what?
I want one of these.
I want this I want to put some of them in the house
I lined them up.
I lined them up!
Light blue
I think I'll get the black one.
Black and blue
Let's make it black and blue
And chicken wings
and
I'll feel sorry for him if he's all alone.
Thank you very much.
Please wait for me.Thank you for your patience.
Yes, I'll be back!
I bought three chopstick rests!
Well, I don't plan to put chopsticks on them.
I'm thinking of putting them on the TV stand.
Wow, it's like a car!
Look at this!
It looks like this.
It's a target with a score on it.
Clang, clang, clang!
Oh, wow!
There's a cork in it.
I want to drop three points.
I wonder if it's that one.
I'd like to go for it.
I missed.
It's definitely not right.
Yay!
Three points down.
Then I'll drop five.
Yes, sir.
I got it.
Wow, it doesn't drop.
Wow.
Wow, it won't hit.
You want to drop five points.
Yay!
Yay.
Five points down.Five points down.
Then I'll go for the last three.
Yes! Yes!
Congratulations!
Can I take this out?
Yes, you may.
I dropped five, three, three, three, two!
Yay!
Ta-da!
This is my dedication!
I got 7 Umaibo and 2 ducks!
They are so cute!
Not many people here.
Maybe because it was a weekday?
Oh, hot spring eggs?
I found some hot spring eggs!
Oh, my gosh! What? Is that what an onsen tamago is?
What? Onsen... what? I'm using it.
That's nice. It looks so nice.
45 degrees.
Really?
Let's touch it.
Oh, but it's hot.
It's hot, yes.
Heh.
Ta-da!
Is it done?
Oh!
I'd like to try onsen tamago for the first time in my life.
Bon appétit.Bon appétit.
Yum.
It's so good!
It's like rice with egg.
Yes, like that.
The soup stock is so delicious.
It's good for your health, too!
Okay, let's move on.
It was delicious!
Surprisingly, some of our fans approached us.
I'm so grateful.
I didn't realize how well they know me.
It's funny.
I don't often go out with my mask off.
I don't get to talk to them at all.
I'm not used to dealing with them.
I'm waving.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
Is this a pickle shop?
Wow.
I'll have to get some pickles for sure.
That's great!
What kind of shop is this?
So you're back again...
Excuse me for disturbing you.
What kind of store is this?
Oh, it's a tsukiya.
A tsukiya...Oh, it was Mr. Makiya.
It was Matakiya.
It said something about a pickle shop.
They have a lot of things. They have miso and so on.
Yes, sir.
Miso?
Which one?
This one?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Big one.
You know what?
I love pickles.
I want to buy some for sure.
Rina Matsuda, a member?
Rina Matsuda loves pickles, too.
We often go to, um...
When we go to Kiho, she always buys pickles for us.
I'll buy this for Matsuda.
Here you go.
Here it is.
Oh, wow.
Is it sweet?
Yeah, it is.
Oh.Ooh.
Ooh.
Wow.
Looks good
No commercial machine.
Mmm-hmm.
Ha-ha-ha.
You made me laugh a little.
Thank you very much.
Like this.
I bought a lot of stuff.
My father, who is a good businessman, put me on his back
I bought so many things!
But there were so many delicious looking things.
It was so hard to decide which one to buy!
Now, let's go to the next one!
Oh, I forgot to buy Ramune!
Let's buy Ramune!
Ramune!
I'll get in line.
Here we go again.
Just a Ramune.
May I? Yes, please.
Just hook an egg on it and drink it.
Thank you very much.
Yay!
He explained about the Ramune very well.
If you tilt it too much, the marble will get stuck and you won't be able to drink it.He said if you tilt it too far, the marbles will get stuck and you won't be able to drink.
I think I'll sit here.
Mmm!
Yum!
It's so good!
Yeah, it's so good.
What is this?
A pie?
Oh, I want some!
Can I?
Hi. - Hi.
Are you okay with YouTube?
Yes, is it okay?
Pancake.
That's great.
Can I have a piece of nori, please?
Yes, ma'am.
The most popular one.
Bon appétit!
Mmm.
The seaweed sticks to it.
Yum.
Bon appétit!
Yum! Delicious!
Yum.
I don't know.
I've never had it before, so I'm really impressed.
It's so good!It's so delicious!
I'm so thirsty.
Hmmm...
You should definitely bring your own drink before coming to this restaurant!
It's so good!
Yeah, it's so good.
Good news for everyone... you can get free tea here.
This is a store that really understands how customers feel. It's a nice store.
Sweet!
It's so cold!
Really, really.
Thank you!
A monkey shows you the hot water.
Look at this!
It looks like a monkey is going to give us a hot bath.
Excuse me for disturbing you.
Oh, wow!
The second one.
Eh, oh no!
Number one.
Cute.
Sorry, everyone. I was just wondering if there was any more emotion or reaction?
You notice that? It's a monkey.
Please don't look at him so calmly, because he is checking the temperature of the water.
So, today, I would like to ask you to let the hot water cool down.
Yes!Yes!
Okay, now let's go to Mr. Puddle Bond.
Se-no, yes!
Yes!
Yes, OK!
Well done!
Yes, go for it!
Yes, we won!
Oh!
Come on, already.
Let's all get a drink!
Let's get them all drunk!
Who's your friend?
You're so cute.
Is this a footbath?
Excuse me.
Is that a footbath?
Is it a footbath?
Is it okay if I go in?
Thank you very much.
All right.
Wow.
It's hot!
It's hot! It's hot! Hot!
Maybe it's a little hot.
Wait a minute.
It's kind of hot in here.
You want to come in?
It's hot!Hot!
Feels good!
Hot!
It feels good, but he's embarrassed to go in here by himself.
Feels good! It's hot! It might be hot!
It's hot!
You should definitely take a footbath in winter.
It should be in winter, but it felt so good!
I found some grilled chicken.
I want some!
I just ate some, but I want some.
Can I eat it?
Can I take a YouTube video?
It's a fetish cover.
How do you like it? Thank you very much.
Right, right, right.
Thank you very much.
Mmm! Delicious!
Mmmm!
Brilliant!
So delicious!
Mmm? So fluffy!
You'll see.
Yum!
It's great.
It's delicious.
Good. - Good.All right. All right.
Let's go.
I'm leaving Kusatsu.
But Rika recommended a place on her show.
She recommended a place there, and I really wanted to go there.
That's partly why I chose Gunma, but I think I'll go to the place I wanted to visit the most.
Let's jump!
Here we are... at Lake Okushima.
Shimagawa? Shimagawa Dam.
As you can see, there's no one here.
I'm scared!
Amazing.
It's amazing, but look, look, look.
You can see it.
Oh, wow.
Isn't it amazing?
This is...
Yay!
It's like a doozy.
Oh, my gosh.
I don't know if you can tell.
It's so big!
Yoo-hoo!
Wow! Oh, my gosh!
It's so loud!
That's great!
Let's have a contest to see which voice makes the most yoo-hoo's.
Okay, let's start with the normal one.
Yoo-hoo!
Okay, a little lower and thicker.Okay, a little lower and thicker.
Wait a minute.
Last one's a cute voice. Here we go.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Is that it? Isn't this the hottest one?
Now, which of these yoo-hoo's was your favorite?
Well, let's head to the next location.
Boom!
Now where are we?
It's pitch black!
Borrow the light from your phone.
This is the place I've always wanted to visit.
But there are a lot of hotels here.
Inns? There are many hotels and inns.
The place I wanted to come... where is it?
Huh! I think I see it!
Whoa!
Look!
Wow! Oh, my gosh! Isn't it amazing?
This is Spirited Away, a Ghibli movie.
They say it may have been modeled after it.
Hey! A fishing boat!
Is there a white one?
Look! It's so beautiful!
I'm crossing! I'm crossing! I'm crossing the bridge!
Master Herc!
Look! I brought towels! The one I bought today!
Ta-da! What do you think?Ta-da! What do you think?
Ta-da! I'm so happy!
Here it is.
Wow! I mean, this place...
It's like a thousand and one questions!
Um, Rin and Sen
Rin and Sen were eating rice balls.
Wow!
I definitely want to stay here someday!
Thank you, Rika!
For showing me such a nice place.
Ok!
Oh!
You can't come here! Get back here!
It's getting late! Come on, before it gets dark!
The lights are on.
I'll buy us some time.
Whew.
Yay! Fun!
There's a scene where Chihiro and Hiroshi hold hands and walk holding their breath.
Well, I'll give it a try.
Deep breath.
Hold it.
I spiritual
Fun
Great enjoyment
I got to do everything I wanted to do!
So how was your trip to heaven?
We arrived at our final destination without incident!
Thank you so much for accompanying my now grown-up Tin-chan on her trip.Thank you for following along on the journey of Tein-chan, who has truly become such an adult.
Thank you for watching!
Please look forward to the second installment!
We have so many places to go!
Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button!
See you soon, everyone!